<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>The COLL_METHOD field for indicator 9-1-1, translated into all languages</message>
	<data>
		<languages>
			<language lang="en"> &lt;p&gt; Indicators are integrated and collected through the two surveys mentioned above. These are surveys under the National Statistical Survey Program. Annually, the General Statistics Office coordinates with relevant ministries and branches to carry out the above surveys and synthesize data of the indicator. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; * Investigate transportation and warehousing: &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Monthly cycle, from 8th to 12th of every month &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Objects, investigation units: Enterprises, HTOs and individual production and business establishments dealing in freight, passenger transport, loading and unloading, warehousing, agents and other services in support of transport of all sugar industries. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Survey content: Revenue from freight, passenger, cargo handling, warehousing, agency and other transport support services; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; * Investigate individual production and business establishments: &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Annual cycle, October 1st. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Subjects and units of investigation: Individual business establishments operating in all branches of the national economy (except agriculture, forestry and fishery). &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Survey content: Number of establishments and employees of individual production and business establishments; Production and business results: assets, capital sources, revenue, budget payment; Specialized information; &lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
			<language lang="vi">&lt;p&gt;Chỉ tiêu được lồng ghép thu thập qua 2 cuộc điều tra nêu trên. Đây là những cuộc điều tra thuộc Chương trình điều tra thống kê quốc gia. Hàng năm,Tổng cục Thống kê phối hợp với các bộ, ngành liên quan để thực hiện các cuộc điều tra trên và tổng hợp số liệu của chỉ tiêu.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Điều tra vận tải kho bãi:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Chu kỳ hàng tháng, từ ngày 08 đến ngày 12 hàng tháng&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Đối tượng, đơn vị điều tra: Doanh nghiệp, HTO và cơ sở sản xuất kinh doanh cá thể kinh doanh vận tải hàng hóa, hành khách, bốc xếp, kho bãi, đại lý và dịch vụ khác hỗ trợ cho vận tải thuộc tất cả các ngành đường.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Nội dung điều tra: Doanh thu vận tải hàng hóa, hành khách, bốc xếp hàng hóa, kho bãi, đại lý và các dịch vụ khác hỗ trợ vận tải;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Điều tra cơ sở sản xuất kinh doanh cá thể:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Chu kỳ hàng năm, ngày 01 tháng 10.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Đối tượng, đơn vị điều tra: Các cơ sở sản xuất kinh doanh cá thể hoạt động trong tất cả các ngành kinh tế quốc dân (trừ ngành nông, lâm nghiệp và thủy sản).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Nội dung điều tra: Số cơ sở và lao động của cơ sở sản xuất kinh doanh cá thể; Kết quả hoạt động sản xuất kinh doanh: tài sản, nguồn vốn, doanh thu, nộp ngân sách; Thông tin chuyên ngành;&lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
</languages>
</data>
</root>
