<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>All metadata fields for the indicator 4-1-4, translated into en</message>
	<data> &lt;p&gt; Goal 4: Ensure quality, equitable, inclusive education and promote lifelong learning opportunities for all &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Target 4.1: By 2030, ensure that all girls and boys complete free, equitable and quality primary and lower secondary education (Global Goal 4.1) &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Indicator 4.1.4. Percentage of students graduating from lower secondary school, percentage of students completing lower secondary level, rate of transition from primary to lower secondary &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; June 2021 &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Ministry of Education and Training &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; No. 35 Dai Co Viet, Hanoi &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; bogddt@moet.gov.vn &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; - Middle school graduation rate is the percentage between the number of students graduating in the last grade of a grade compared to the number of students in the final grade that are eligible for graduation. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Middle school completion rate is the percentage between the number of students graduating from middle school in the school year (t + 3) to the number of students in the 6th grade at the beginning of the school year (t). &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Primary to lower secondary school transition rate is the percentage of the number of students newly enrolled in grade 6 during the school year (t+1) to the number of students who are recognized to have completed elementary school. school year (t). &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; The list of administrative units in Vietnam issued together with the Prime Minister&apos;s Decision No. 124/2004/QD-TTg dated July 8, 2004 and the changes updated by the General Statistics Office to date December 31, 2019) &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Statistical reporting mode issued by the Ministry of Education and Training. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; The Departments of Education and Training of the provinces/cities directly under the Central Government collect information on the forms: 02-TH-DN; 03-High School-DN; 02-TH-CN; 03-THCS-CN and send it to the Ministry of Education and Training to calculate the quota. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Year &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Ministry of Education and Training &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Ministry of Education and Training &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; The indicator reflects the graduation level of lower secondary students, which is the basis for assessing the teaching and learning quality of lower secondary education. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Only figures for 2019 &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; (Published source: 2020 national report on 5-year progress towards implementation of sustainable development goals. Data from the Ministry of Education and Training) &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Indicator “Rate of students graduating from lower secondary school; the rate of students completing lower secondary school, the rate of transition from primary to lower secondary school” is one of Vietnam&apos;s indicators to represent the global sustainable development indicator “&lt;strong&gt; 4.1. 1: &lt;/strong&gt; Proportion of children and young people: (a) in grades 2/3; (b) at the end of primary; and (c) at the end of lower secondary achieving at least a minimum proficiency level in (i) reading and (ii) mathematics, by sex” &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; However, the indicator does not guarantee global comparability because the content, scope and calculation method of Vietnam are not the same as the global standard. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; - Circular No. 03/2019/TT-BKHĐT dated January 22, 2019 stipulating the set of statistical indicators for sustainable development of Vietnam; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Circular No. 24/2018/TT-BGDĐT dated September 28, 2018 of the Ministry of Education and Training on promulgating the reporting regime for statistics of the Education and Training sector. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://unstats.un.org/sdgs/metadat/&quot;&gt; https://unstats.un.org/sdgs/metadat/ &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</data>
</root>
