<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>The STAT_CONC_DEF field for indicator 16-6-1, translated into en</message>
	<data> &lt;p&gt; Public services are activities serving the common and essential interests, basic rights and obligations of organizations and citizens, directly performed by the State or transferred to non-State establishments. for efficiency and fairness. Public services are activities of state agencies in performing state administrative management functions and ensuring the supply of public goods to serve the common and essential needs of society. The implementation of such activities can be undertaken by the state or the private sector. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; Public services include 3 types: Public services in the field of non-business; public services in the field of public utilities and public services in the field of state administration, also known as public administrative services. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; Public non-business services include activities that provide essential social welfare for the people such as: Education, culture, science, health care, physical training and sports, insurance, social security, ... &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; Public services are activities that provide basic and essential goods and services for people and communities such as: environmental sanitation, waste treatment, clean water supply, urban public transport, natural disaster prevention,... Some activities can be carried out by the private sector such as: Environmental sanitation, clean water supply. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; Public administrative service is a service associated with the state management function to meet the requirements of the people. This is part of the state management function. To perform this function, the state must carry out direct service activities such as licensing, certificates, registration, notarization, visas, civil status,... &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; The most recent percentage of the population satisfied with public services is the percentage of the population that was satisfied with public services in the most recent survey of the total population. &lt;/p&gt;</data>
</root>
