<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>The STAT_CONC_DEF field for indicator 9-4-1, translated into all languages</message>
	<data>
		<languages>
			<language lang="en"> &lt;p&gt; Expenditure on science and technology is the total internal expenditure in the territory of Vietnam in a certain period, including expenditures on science and technology (scientific research, research and development activities). experimentation, technology development, technology application, science and technology services, promotion of initiatives and other creative activities for the development of science and technology) in the territory of Vietnam from all sources but excluding expenses for science and technology invested by Vietnamese organizations and individuals outside the Vietnamese territory (referred to as total domestic expenditure on science and technology). &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; Total domestic expenditure on science and technology is measured by summing up the internal expenditures of the entities performing the expenditure on science and technology activities (internal expenditure of: Scientific research organizations). science and technology development; higher education institutions; science and technology service organizations; administrative agencies and other non-business units; enterprises and the not-for-profit sector). &lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
			<language lang="vi">&lt;p&gt;Chi cho khoa học và công nghệ là tổng chi tiêu nội bộ trên lãnh thổ Việt Nam trong một thời kỳ nhất định, bao gồm cả các chi tiêu cho khoa học và công nghệ (hoạt động nghiên cứu khoa học, nghiên cứu và triển khai thực nghiệm, phát triển công nghệ, ứng dụng công nghệ, dịch vụ khoa học và công nghệ, phát huy sáng kiến và hoạt động sáng tạo khác nhằm phát triển khoa học và công nghệ) trên lãnh thổ Việt Nam từ tất cả các nguồn nhưng loại trừ chi phí cho khoa học và công nghệ do tổ chức, cá nhân người Việt Nam đầu tư ở ngoài lãnh thổ Việt Nam (gọi là tổng chi quốc nội cho khoa học và công nghệ).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tổng chi quốc nội cho khoa học và công nghệ được đo lường bằng cách cộng tổng các chi tiêu nội bộ của các đối tượng thực hiện chi cho hoạt động khoa học và công nghệ (chi tiêu nội bộ của: Tổ chức nghiên cứu khoa học và phát triển công nghệ; cơ sở giáo dục đại học; tổ chức dịch vụ khoa học và công nghệ; cơ quan hành chính và đơn vị sự nghiệp khác; doanh nghiệp và khu vực phi lợi nhuận). &lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
</languages>
</data>
</root>
