<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>The COMPARABILITY field for indicator 8-10-2, translated into all languages</message>
	<data>
		<languages>
			<language lang="en"> &lt;p&gt; This indicator corresponds to the global SDG target “8.10.2: Proportion of adults (15 years and older) with an account at a bank or other financial institution or with a mobile-money-service provider”. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; However, the scope of the Viet Nam indicator is narrower than the global target. Vietnam can only calculate data of people who have accounts at banks and foreign bank branches. While globally regulated: An account at a financial institution includes an account at a bank or at another type of financial institution, such as a credit union, microfinance institution, cooperative or post office (if applicable). In addition, those who have a payroll account, government wire transfer or payment for agricultural products to an account at a financial institution in the past 12 months; payment of utility bills or tuition fees from an account at a financial institution in the past 12 months; GSM Association&apos;s mobile money account (GSMA) for non-banking services (MMU) for the past 12 months to pay bills or send or receive money. &lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
			<language lang="vi">&lt;p&gt;Chỉ tiêu này tương ứng với chỉ tiêu SDG toàn cầu “8.10.2: Proportion of adults (15 years and older) with an account at a bank or other financial institution or with a mobile-money-service provider”. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tuy nhiên phạm vi của chỉ tiêu của Việt Nam hẹp hơn chỉ tiêu toàn cầu. Việt Nam chỉ tính toán được số liệu của những người có tài khoản tại ngân hàng, chi nhánh ngân hàng nước ngoài. Trong khi toàn cầu quy định:Tài khoản tại một tổ chức tài chính bao gồm tài khoản tại ngân hàng hoặc tại một loại tổ chức tài chính khác, chẳng hạn như liên minh tín dụng, tổ chức tài chính vi mô, hợp tác xã hoặc bưu điện (nếu có).Ngoài ra, còn bao gồm những người có tài khoản tiền lương, chuyển khoản của chính phủ hoặc thanh toán cho các sản phẩm nông nghiệp vào tài khoản tại một tổ chức tài chính trong 12 tháng qua; thanh toán hóa đơn điện nước hoặc học phí từ tài khoản tại một tổ chức tài chính trong 12 tháng qua; tài khoản tiền điện thoại di động của Hiệp hội GSM (GSMA) cho các dịch vụ không qua ngân hàng (MMU) trong 12 tháng qua để thanh toán hóa đơn hoặc gửi hoặc nhận tiền.&lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
</languages>
</data>
</root>
