<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>The COMPARABILITY field for indicator 8-5-1, translated into all languages</message>
	<data>
		<languages>
			<language lang="en"> &lt;p&gt; This indicator corresponds to the global SDG target 8.5.1: Average hourly earnings of employees, by sex, age, occupation and persons with disabilities &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; There are some differences between the Vietnam indicator and the global indicator: &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; + Global average hourly earnings; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; + Vietnam calculates average monthly income. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; Global disaggregated by people with disabilities; Vietnam has not calculated according to this sub-category. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; In addition, the diversity of data sources also greatly affects international comparability, as each source type has its own scope and characteristics. It is not entirely accurate to compare, for example, the hourly earnings from the labor census for one country with the hourly earnings from the enterprise census for another country. The use of non-standard definitions and heterogeneity of criteria leads to no guarantee of international comparison. &lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
			<language lang="vi">&lt;p&gt;Chỉ tiêu này tương ứng với chỉ tiêu SDG toàn cầu 8.5.1: Average hourly earnings of employees, by sex, age, occupation and persons with disabilities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Có một số khác biệt giữa chỉ tiêu Việt Nam và chỉ tiêu toàn cầu:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;+ Toàn cầu tính thu nhập trung bình theo giờ; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;+ Việt Nam tính thu nhập trung bình theo tháng.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Toàn cầu có phân tổ theo người khuyết tật; Việt Nam chưa tính toán được theo phân tổ này.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ngoài ra, sự đa dạng của các nguồn số liệu cũng ảnh hưởng rất lớn đến khả năng so sánh quốc tế, vì mỗi loại nguồn có phạm vi và đặc điểm riêng. Sẽ không hoàn toàn chính xác nếu so sánh, ví dụ, thu nhập hàng giờ từ điều tra lao động cho một quốc gia với thu nhập hàng giờ từ điều tra doanh nghiệp, cơ sở sản xuất kinh doanh cho một quốc gia khác. Việc sử dụng các định nghĩa không chuẩn và sự không đồng nhất của các tiêu chí dẫn đến không bảo đảm so sánh quốc tế.&lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
</languages>
</data>
</root>
