<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>The STAT_CONC_DEF field for indicator 1-2-5, translated into all languages</message>
	<data>
		<languages>
			<language lang="en"> &lt;p&gt; Subjects cared for and raised at social protection establishments and social houses, including: &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; (1) Social protection beneficiaries with extremely difficult circumstances include: &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; a) Children under difficult circumstances who cannot take care of themselves and have no one to receive care and nurture in the community, including: &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; Children under 16 years of age who do not have a source of nourishment in one of the following cases: &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Abandoned without adoption; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Orphaned both father and mother; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Orphaned father or mother and the other missing as prescribed by law; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Orphaned father or mother and the other who is enjoying the care and nurturing regime at social protection establishments or social houses; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Orphaned father or mother and the other being while serving a prison sentence in prison or serving a decision on handling of administrative violations at reformatory, compulsory education institution, rehabilitation facility compulsive addiction; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Both parents are missing as prescribed by law; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Both parents are enjoying the care and nurturing regime at social protection establishments or social houses; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Both parents are serving prison sentences in prisons or are serving decisions on handling of administrative violations at reformatories, compulsory education establishments, compulsory detoxification establishments; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - The parent is missing as prescribed by law and the other person is enjoying the care and nurturing regime at a social protection establishment or social house; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - The parent is missing as prescribed by law and the other is serving a prison sentence at a prison or is serving a decision on handling of administrative violations at a reformatory or educational institution compulsory, compulsory detoxification establishments; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - One parent is enjoying the care and nurturing regime at a social protection establishment or social house and the other is serving a prison sentence at a prison or is serving a decision on handling of violations. administrative offenses at reformatory schools, compulsory educational institutions, compulsory detoxification establishments. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; HIV-infected children from poor households; HIV-infected people from poor households who are no longer able to work without pension, monthly social insurance allowance, monthly preferential allowance for meritorious people, or other monthly allowance. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; b) The elderly are cared for and raised at social protection establishments or social houses in accordance with the law on elderly people; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; c) Disabled children and disabled people are cared for and raised at social protection establishments and social houses in accordance with the law on disabled people. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; (2) Objects needing urgent protection include: &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; a) Victims of domestic violence, victims of sexual abuse, victims of trafficking, victims of forced labor; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; b) Children and street people begging for food while waiting to be taken back to their places of residence; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; c) Other objects in need of urgent protection as decided by the Chairman of the provincial People&apos;s Committee. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; (3) Subjects who voluntarily live in social protection establishments and social houses include: &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; a) The elderly perform under the care delegation contract; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; b) Persons not specified in items (1) and (2) have no conditions to live at home and wish to live in social protection establishments or social houses. &lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
			<language lang="vi">&lt;p&gt;Đối tượng được chăm sóc, nuôi dưỡng tại cơ sở bảo trợ xã hội, nhà xã hội, gồm:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1) Đối tượng bảo trợ xã hội có hoàn cảnh đặc biệt khó khăn bao gồm:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a) Đối tượng trẻ em thuộc diện khó khăn không tự lo được cuộc sống và không có người nhận chăm sóc, nuôi dưỡng tại cộng đồng, gồm:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trẻ em dưới 16 tuổi không có nguồn nuôi dưỡng thuộc một trong các trường hợp quy định sau đây:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Bị bỏ rơi chưa có người nhận làm con nuôi;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Mồ côi cả cha và mẹ;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Mồ côi cha hoặc mẹ và người còn lại mất tích theo quy định của pháp luật;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Mồ côi cha hoặc mẹ và người còn lại đang hưởng chế độ chăm sóc, nuôi dưỡng tại cơ sở bảo trợ xã hội, nhà xã hội;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Mồ côi cha hoặc mẹ và người còn lại đang trong thời gian chấp hành án phạt tù tại trại giam hoặc đang chấp hành quyết định xử lý vi phạm hành chính tại trường giáo dưỡng, cơ sở giáo dục bắt buộc, cơ sở cai nghiện bắt buộc;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Cả cha và mẹ mất tích theo quy định của pháp luật;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Cả cha và mẹ đang hưởng chế độ chăm sóc, nuôi dưỡng tại cơ sở bảo trợ xã hội, nhà xã hội;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Cả cha và mẹ đang trong thời gian chấp hành án phạt tù tại trại giam hoặc đang chấp hành quyết định xử lý vi phạm hành chính tại trường giáo dưỡng, cơ sở giáo dục bắt buộc, cơ sở cai nghiện bắt buộc;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Cha hoặc mẹ mất tích theo quy định của pháp luật và người còn lại đang hưởng chế độ chăm sóc, nuôi dưỡng tại cơ sở bảo trợ xã hội, nhà xã hội;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Cha hoặc mẹ mất tích theo quy định của pháp luật và người còn lại đang trong thời gian chấp hành án phạt tù tại trại giam hoặc đang chấp hành quyết định xử lý vi phạm hành chính tại trường giáo dưỡng, cơ sở giáo dục bắt buộc, cơ sở cai nghiện bắt buộc;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Cha hoặc mẹ đang hưởng chế độ chăm sóc, nuôi dưỡng tại cơ sở bảo trợ xã hội, nhà xã hội và người còn lại đang trong thời gian chấp hành án phạt tù tại trại giam hoặc đang chấp hành quyết định xử lý vi phạm hành chính tại trường giáo dưỡng, cơ sở giáo dục bắt buộc, cơ sở cai nghiện bắt buộc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trẻ em bị nhiễm HIV thuộc hộ nghèo; người bị nhiễm HIV thuộc hộ nghèo không còn khả năng lao động mà không có lương hưu, trợ cấp bảo hiểm xã hội hàng tháng, trợ cấp ưu đãi người có công hàng tháng, trợ cấp hàng tháng khác.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b) Người cao tuổi thuộc diện được chăm sóc, nuôi dưỡng tại cơ sở bảo trợ xã hội, nhà xã hội theo quy định của pháp luật về người cao tuổi;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;c) Trẻ em khuyết tật, người khuyết tật thuộc diện được chăm sóc, nuôi dưỡng tại cơ sở bảo trợ xã hội, nhà xã hội theo quy định của pháp luật về người khuyết tật.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(2) Đối tượng cần bảo vệ khẩn cấp bao gồm:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a) Nạn nhân của bạo lực gia đình, nạn nhân bị xâm hại tình dục, nạn nhân bị buôn bán, nạn nhân bị cưỡng bức lao động;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b) Trẻ em, người lang thang xin ăn trong thời gian chờ đưa về nơi cư trú;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;c) Đối tượng cần bảo vệ khẩn cấp khác theo quyết định của Chủ tịch Ủy ban nhân dân cấp tỉnh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(3) Đối tượng tự nguyện sống tại cơ sở bảo trợ xã hội, nhà xã hội bao gồm:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a) Người cao tuổi thực hiện theo hợp đồng ủy nhiệm chăm sóc;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b) Người không thuộc diện quy định tại mục (1) và mục (2) không có điều kiện sống tại gia đình, có nhu cầu vào sống tại cơ sở bảo trợ xã hội, nhà xã hội.&lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
</languages>
</data>
</root>
