<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>The COLL_METHOD field for indicator 5-2-2, translated into en</message>
	<data> &lt;p&gt; The National Survey on Violence Against Women in Vietnam 2019 consists of three components: quantitative research; qualitative research; and economic damage caused by violence against women. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; The quantitative component of this survey (“survey”) was conducted by the GSO (including the review and testing of the questionnaire, training of enumerators, and data collection and processing). The quantitative survey includes household surveys in a nationally representative sample in all six regions of Vietnam. A multi-level sample design was used to sample 6,000 households. A total of 5,976 women between the ages of 15 and 64 were interviewed directly by trained enumerators. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; The qualitative component was implemented by the Center for Initiatives in Health and Population (CCIHP). Qualitative research aims to: understand the context of husband/partner violence against women; compare with quantitative results; in-depth analysis and interpretation of quantitative results; and explore problems that cannot be studied by quantitative methods. Data were collected through in-depth interviews, key informant interviews and focus group discussions. A total of 269 participants, including women with disabilities and ethnic minority women, 11 key informants, provided information and shared their experiences for qualitative research. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; Finally, the research component on economic damage caused by violence against women was conducted by UNFPA Viet Nam in cooperation with a number of national and international consultants. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; UNFPA Viet Nam managed the entire process with technical support from the kNOwVAWdata Initiative (a partnership between the UNFPA Asia Pacific office and the Government of Australia). &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; More information about this investigation can be found at this link: https://vietnam.unfpa.org/sites/default/files/pub-pdf/0._bao_cao_chinh_0.pdf &lt;/p&gt;</data>
</root>
