<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>The COLL_METHOD field for indicator 8-7-1, translated into all languages</message>
	<data>
		<languages>
			<language lang="en"> &lt;p&gt; The 2018 National Child Labor Survey was conducted in conjunction with the Labor-Employment Survey 2018, conducted by the General Statistics Office in November and December 2018 with a sample size of 38280 households. families nationwide in 2552 enumeration areas. The employment and labor statistics in this survey are applying the statistical standards of economic activity, employment, unemployment and underemployment recommended by the ILO at the International Conference on Statistics. the 13th labor force in 1982 (ICLS 13). &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; The results of the survey collected information on 29192 children aged 5-17 years old. All information collected from the child labor survey is checked, cleaned, coded and entered by GSO. The survey form of each province is assigned to the first and second time data entry staff by two different people. Input data is cross-matched between the two data entries to ensure the final data is consistent between the two data entries. After the final data is available, the data is cleaned for the last time on the computer to ensure completeness, accuracy and logic between the data fields. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; All data of the survey was handed over by GSO to the Ministry of Labour, Invalids and Social Affairs for technical processing by the Institute of Labor and Social Sciences (ILSSA), the Ministry of Labour, Invalids and Social Affairs, analysis and report generation. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; For more information about the child labor investigation, please visit the following link: https://www.ilo.org/wcmsp5/groups/public/---asia/---ro-bangkok/---ilo -hanoi/documents/publication/wcms_764355.pdf &lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
			<language lang="vi">&lt;p&gt;Cuộc điều tra quốc gia về lao động trẻ em 2018 được tiến hành kết hợp với cuộc điều tra Lao động-Việc làm 2018, do Tổng cục Thống kê tiến hành trong tháng 11 và 12 năm 2018 với quy mô mẫu là 38280 hộ gia đình trên toàn quốc thuộc 2552 địa bàn điều tra. Công tác thống kê lao động, việc làm trong cuộc điều tra này đang áp dụng các tiêu chuẩn thống kê dân số hoạt động kinh tế, việc làm, thất nghiệp và thiếu việc làm được ILO khuyến nghị tại Hội nghị quốc tế về thống kê lao động lần thứ 13 năm 1982 (ICLS 13).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kết quả cuộc điều tra đã thu thập thông tin của 29192 trẻ em trong độ tuổi từ 5-17 tuổi. Toàn bộ thông tin thu thập được từ cuộc điều tra về lao động trẻ em được GSO nghiệm thu, làm sạch, đánh mã và nhập tin. Phiếu điều tra của mỗi tỉnh được phân công cán bộ nhập tin lần 1 và lần 2 bởi hai người khác nhau. Dữ liệu nhập tin được đối chiếu chéo giữa 2 lần nhập tin để bảo đảm dữ liệu cuối cùng bảo đảm thống nhất giữa 2 lần nhập tin. Sau khi có dữ liệu cuối cùng, dữ liệu được làm sạch lần cuối trên máy tính để bảo đảm tính đầy đủ, tính chính xác và tính logic giữa các trường dữ liệu.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Toàn bộ dữ liệu của cuộc điều tra được GSO bàn giao cho Bộ Lao động, Thương binh và Xã hội để Viện Khoa học Lao động và Xã hội (ILSSA), Bộ Lao động, Thương binh và Xã hội xử lý kỹ thuật, phân tích và xây dựng báo cáo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thông tin chi tiết về điều tra lao động trẻ em truy cập tại đường link: https://www.ilo.org/wcmsp5/groups/public/---asia/---ro-bangkok/---ilo-hanoi/documents/publication/wcms_764355.pdf&lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
</languages>
</data>
</root>
