<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>The COLL_METHOD field for indicator 3-1-4, translated into all languages</message>
	<data>
		<languages>
			<language lang="en"> &lt;p&gt; The General Statistics Office coordinated with the Ministry of Health to conduct a sampling survey to collect information; The Ministry of Justice collects information through the civil status registration system and sends it to the General Statistics Office. The General Statistics Office synthesizes data from two sources and publishes the targets. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; * Current data source obtained through the results of the 2014 Child and Women Targeted Survey (MICS): &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; The Viet Nam MICS Survey 2014 is part of the Global MICS Program, conducted by the General Statistics Office in collaboration with the United Nations Children&apos;s Fund from the end of December 2013 to April 2014. technical and financial support for this investigation. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; The sample of the Vietnam MICS 2014 survey is designed to provide reliable estimates of multiple indicators of children and women at the national, urban/rural and six-regional levels. The Vietnam MICS 2014 survey had a sample size of 10018 interviewed households, with 9827 women and 3316 children interviewed. &lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
			<language lang="vi">&lt;p&gt;Tổng cục Thống kê phối hợp với Bộ Y tế thực hiện điều tra chọn mẫu để thu thập thông tin; Bộ Tư pháp thu thập thông tin qua hệ thống đăng ký hộ tịch và gửi về Tổng cục Thống kê. Tổng cục Thống kê tổng hợp số liệu từ 2 nguồn và công bố chỉ tiêu.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Nguồn số liệu hiện tại thu qua Kết quả điều tra đánh giá các mục tiêu trẻ em và phụ nữ năm 2014 (MICS): &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Điều tra MICS Việt Nam 2014 là một bộ phận của Chương trình MICS toàn cầu, do Tổng cục Thống kê phối hợp với Quỹ Nhi đồng Liên hợp quốc thực hiện vào cuối tháng 12 năm 2013 đến tháng 4 năm 2014. UNICEF cung cấp các hỗ trợ kỹ thuật và tài chính cho cuộc điều tra này.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mẫu của điều tra MICS Việt Nam 2014 được thiết kế nhằm cung cấp các ước lượng tin cậy cho nhiều chỉ tiêu về trẻ em và phụ nữ ở cấp quốc gia, thành thị/nông thôn và 6 vùng. Điều tra MICS Việt Nam 2014 có cỡ mẫu là 10018 hộ gia đình được phỏng vấn, với 9827 phụ nữ và 3316 trẻ em được phỏng vấn.&lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
</languages>
</data>
</root>
