<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>The COLL_METHOD field for indicator 9-2-1, translated into all languages</message>
	<data>
		<languages>
			<language lang="en"> &lt;p&gt; The indicator is integrated and collected through 2 surveys conducted by the General Statistics Office. These are surveys under the National Statistical Survey Program, specifically: &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; * Enterprise investigation &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Investigation object, unit: &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; Independent economic accounting corporations, corporations, enterprises/cooperatives are established and are regulated by the Law on Enterprises and the Law on Cooperatives; the grassroots units directly under the enterprise have come into production and business activities. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Survey type: &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; Comprehensive survey combined with sample survey &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Investigation content: &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; + Number of businesses; number of employees, capital, revenue, profit, budget payment, investment capital; credit financing; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; + Assets and specialized economic information; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Period, time of investigation: &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; Annual cycle, March 1st. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; * Investigate individual production and business establishments &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Subjects and units of investigation: Individual business establishments operating in all branches of the national economy (except agriculture, forestry and fisheries). &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Type of investigation: Survey of all sample combinations &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Investigation content: &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; + Number of establishments and employees of individual production and business establishments; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; + Production and business results: assets, capital, revenue, budget payment; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; + Specialized information; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Survey period and time: Annual cycle, October 1st. &lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
			<language lang="vi">&lt;p&gt;Chỉ tiêu được lồng ghép thu thập qua 2 cuộc điều tra do Tổng cục Thống kê thực hiện. Đây là những cuộc điều tra thuộc Chương trình điều tra thống kê quốc gia, cụ thể:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Điều tra doanh nghiệp&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Đối tượng, đơn vị điều tra:&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Các Tập đoàn, Tổng công ty, doanh nghiệp/HTX hạch toán kinh tế độc lập được thành lập, chịu sự điều tiết bởi Luật Doanh nghiệp, Luật HTX; các đơn vị cơ sở trực thuộc doanh nghiệp đã đi vào hoạt động sản xuất kinh doanh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Loại điều tra:&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Điều tra toàn bộ kết hợp điều tra chọn mẫu&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Nội dung điều tra: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;+ Số lượng doanh nghiệp; số lao động, nguồn vốn, doanh thu, lợi nhuận, nộp ngân sách, vốn đầu tư; tài chính, tín dụng;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;+ Tài sản và các thông tin chuyên ngành kinh tế;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; - Thời kỳ, thời điểm điều tra:&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Chu kỳ hàng năm, ngày 01 tháng 3.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Điều tra cơ sở sản xuất kinh doanh cá thể&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Đối tượng, đơn vị điều tra: Các cơ sở sản xuất kinh doanh cá thể hoạt động trong tất cả các ngành kinh tế quốc dân (trừ ngành nông, lâm nghiệp và thuỷ sản).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Loại điều tra: Điều tra toàn bộ kết hợp chọn mẫu&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Nội dung điều tra: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;+ Số cơ sở và lao động của cơ sở sản xuất kinh doanh cá thể;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;+ Kết quả hoạt động sản xuất kinh doanh: tài sản, nguồn vốn, doanh thu, nộp ngân sách;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;+ Thông tin chuyên ngành;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Thời kỳ, thời điểm điều tra: Chu kỳ hàng năm, ngày 01 tháng 10.&lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
</languages>
</data>
</root>
