<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>All metadata fields for the indicator 17-1-1, translated into en</message>
	<data> &lt;p&gt; Goal 17: Strengthen implementation and promote global partnerships for sustainable development &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Goal 17.1: Promote a multilateral, open, non-discriminatory, fair and international law-based trading system within the framework of the World Trade Organization, including promoting an end to it Negotiating Doha Development Agenda (global 17.10 target) &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Indicator 17.1.1. Average import tax rate &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; June 2021 &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Ministry of Finance &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; No. 28 Tran Hung Dao - Hoan Kiem District - Hanoi &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; support@mof.gov.vn &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; The average import tax rate is the average tax rate applied to goods imported into Vietnam according to the List of Vietnam&apos;s imports and exports. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; The average import tax rate is calculated by the weighted average method, using the weighted method based on the value of imported goods. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Vietnam product industry system promulgated under Decision No. 43/2018/QD-TTg dated November 1, 2018 of the Prime Minister &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Administrative data of the Ministry of Finance. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; 2 years &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Ministry of Finance &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Ministry of Finance &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; The indicator reflects the average tariff rate that a quantity of foreign goods is brought into the Vietnamese market. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; 2020 framework data only &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; (Published source: 2020 national report on 5-year progress towards implementation of sustainable development goals. Data from the Ministry of Finance) &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Corresponding global level indicator “17.10.1: Worldwide weighted tariff-average” &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; - Circular No. 03/2019/TT-BKHDT dated January 22, 2019 stipulating the set of statistical indicators for sustainable development of Vietnam; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://unstats.un.org/sdgs/metadata/&quot;&gt; https://unstats.un.org/sdgs/metadata/ &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</data>
</root>
