<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>The REC_USE_LIM field for indicator 5-2-2, translated into en</message>
	<data> &lt;p&gt; This survey is not part of the National Statistical Survey Program and has only been conducted in Vietnam twice, in 2010 and 2019. In 2019, Vietnam conducted the second National Census, using method of the World Health Organization (WHO) Multinational Survey on Women&apos;s Health and Domestic Violence, and with some modifications. This method was also used for the 2010 Census. The results of this Census are the basis for Vietnam to know what has and has not changed, as well as what to do to get change in the right direction. Future. The scope of this Survey is wider, including expanding the age range from 15 to 64 years old. The issue of violence is also studied beyond the family, extending to the workplace and other public spaces. Violence against Viet Nam&apos;s most vulnerable female populations is particularly focused, in particular ethnic minority women, women and girls with disabilities. Economic losses have been calculated, showing clearly how much the country has lost economically as a result of violence against women and girls. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; The national survey on violence against women in Vietnam was conducted by the Ministry of Labour, Invalids and Social Affairs (LOLISA) in collaboration with the General Statistics Office (GSO). This investigation was supported by UNFPA within the framework of the project “Support for the development and implementation of evidence-based and human rights-based policies and programs to prevent and respond to gender-based violence, domestic violence and dealing with problems related to prostitution” and was supported by technical and financial support from the Government of Australia through the Department of Foreign Affairs and Trade (DFAT) and UNFPA. This entire investigation was supported and funded by the Government of Australia through the Department of Foreign Affairs and Trade (DFAT) and UNFPA. &lt;/p&gt;</data>
</root>
