<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>The COLL_METHOD field for indicator 3-1-1, translated into en</message>
	<data> &lt;p&gt; The indicator “Maternal mortality rate per hundred thousand live births” is compiled from the data of the Population and Housing Census (10-year cycle) &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Survey type: Comprehensive survey combined with sample survey &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Investigation content: &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; * Complete survey: The complete survey is carried out for the subjects of the survey units to collect basic information on population and housing. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; * Sampling survey: &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; + Sampling survey was carried out for a part of the population of Vietnam for the purpose of expanding the content of the survey, meeting the requirements of in-depth analytical information; help improve the quality of investigation, especially for sensitive and complex questions; help save the cost of the Census. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; + Sampling survey applied two-stage stratified sampling method. Stage 1: Determine the number of EAs to be sampled in each district according to the method of distribution proportional to the square root of the size and select the sample EAs of each district according to the probability method proportional to the size ; Stage 2: Select a household sample from the list of households in the sample survey area. Sample households are selected systematically according to distance. The number of selected EAs accounts for about 40% of the total enumeration areas in the country. The number of sample households surveyed accounted for about 10% of the total number of households nationwide. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - Information collection method: The Census used two methods of collecting information: face-to-face interviews and households provided information on the Census website. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; + Direct interview method: The enumerator went to each household to ask the informant and recorded all the answers on the electronic questionnaire designed on a tablet or smartphone (write e-vouchers for short); In case of force majeure for a few enumeration areas where information technology cannot be applied in data collection, the enumerators shall use paper slips to record information. For those who are temporarily absent during the survey period, the enumerator can ask other people in the household, or rely on documents provided by relatives or the government to record the questionnaire. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; When collecting information on housing, the enumerator asked the informant in combination with direct observation of the house or apartment to record the answers on the questionnaire. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; + Households provide information on the website of the Census: Households are provided with an account and password to log in and provide information on the survey form on the website of the Census (short form and online ballot). The self-information method is applied to the short form. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; For more information about the investigation plan follow the following link: https://www.gso.gov.vn/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/2.Phuong-an-TDT-2019.pdf &lt;/p&gt;</data>
</root>
