<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>The STAT_CONC_DEF field for indicator 16-6-1, translated into all languages</message>
	<data>
		<languages>
			<language lang="en"> &lt;p&gt; Public services are activities serving the common and essential interests, basic rights and obligations of organizations and citizens, directly performed by the State or transferred to non-State establishments. for efficiency and fairness. Public services are activities of state agencies in performing state administrative management functions and ensuring the supply of public goods to serve the common and essential needs of society. The implementation of such activities can be undertaken by the state or the private sector. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; Public services include 3 types: Public services in the field of non-business; public services in the field of public utilities and public services in the field of state administration, also known as public administrative services. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; Public non-business services include activities that provide essential social welfare for the people such as: Education, culture, science, health care, physical training and sports, insurance, social security, ... &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; Public services are activities that provide basic and essential goods and services for people and communities such as: environmental sanitation, waste treatment, clean water supply, urban public transport, natural disaster prevention,... Some activities can be carried out by the private sector such as: Environmental sanitation, clean water supply. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; Public administrative service is a service associated with the state management function to meet the requirements of the people. This is part of the state management function. To perform this function, the state must carry out direct service activities such as licensing, certificates, registration, notarization, visas, civil status,... &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; The most recent percentage of the population satisfied with public services is the percentage of the population that was satisfied with public services in the most recent survey of the total population. &lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
			<language lang="vi">&lt;p&gt;Dịch vụ công là những hoạt động phục vụ các lợi ích chung, thiết yếu, các quyền và nghĩa vụ cơ bản của tổ chức và công dân do Nhà nước trực tiếp thực hiện hoặc chuyển giao cho các cơ sở ngoài Nhà nước thực hiện nhằm mục tiêu hiệu quả và công bằng. Dịch vụ công là những hoạt động của cơ quan nhà nước trong việc thực thi chức năng quản lý hành chính nhà nước và bảo đảm cung ứng các hàng hóa công cộng phục vụ nhu cầu chung, thiết yếu của xã hội. Việc tiến hành hoạt động ấy có thể do nhà nước hoặc tư nhân đảm nhiệm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dịch vụ công gồm 3 loại: Dịch vụ công trong lĩnh vực sự nghiệp; dịch vụ công trong lĩnh vực công ích và dịch vụ công trong lĩnh vực hành chính nhà nước hay còn gọi là dịch vụ hành chính công.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dịch vụ sự nghiệp công gồm các hoạt động cung cấp phúc lợi xã hội thiết yếu cho người dân như: Giáo dục, văn hóa, khoa học, chăm sóc sức khỏe, thể dục thể thao, bảo hiểm, an sinh xã hội,... &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dịch vụ công ích là các hoạt động cung cấp hàng hóa, dịch vụ cơ bản, thiết yếu cho người dân và cộng đồng như: Vệ sinh môi trường, xử lý rác thải, cấp nước sạch, vận tải công cộng đô thị, phòng chống thiên tai,... Một số hoạt động khu vực tư nhân có thể đảm nhiệm như: Vệ sinh môi trường, cung ứng nước sạch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dịch vụ hành chính công là loại dịch vụ gắn liền với chức năng quản lý nhà nước nhằm đáp ứng yêu cầu của người dân. Đây là một phần trong chức năng quản lý nhà nước. Để thực hiện chức năng này, nhà nước phải tiến hành những hoạt động phục vụ trực tiếp như cấp giấy phép, giấy chứng nhận, đăng ký, công chứng, thị thực, hộ tịch,...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tỷ lệ dân số hài lòng về dịch vụ công trong lần gần đây nhất là tỷ lệ phần trăm dân số hài lòng về dịch vụ công trong lần gần đây nhất trong tổng số người dân được được khảo sát.&lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
</languages>
</data>
</root>
