<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<mes:GenericMetadata xmlns:mes="http://www.sdmx.org/resources/sdmxml/schemas/v2_1/message" xmlns:gen="http://www.sdmx.org/resources/sdmxml/schemas/v2_1/metadata/generic" xmlns:com="http://www.sdmx.org/resources/sdmxml/schemas/v2_1/common">
  <mes:Header>
    <mes:ID>MESSAGE_ID_PLACEHOLDER</mes:ID>
    <mes:Test>false</mes:Test>
    <mes:Prepared>2021-07-21T22:20:54.960Z</mes:Prepared>
    <mes:Sender id="sender"/>
    <mes:Structure structureID="MDS1">
      <com:Structure>
        <URN>urn:sdmx:org.sdmx.infomodel.metadatastructure.MetadataStructure=IAEG-SDGs:SDG_MSD(0.3)</URN>
      </com:Structure>
    </mes:Structure>
  </mes:Header>
  <mes:MetadataSet structureRef="MDS1" setID="943c5268-d414-43d4-a748-4531db8d1791">
    <com:Name xml:lang="en">SDG METADATA SET</com:Name>
    <gen:Report id="SDG_META_RPT">
      <gen:Target id="KEY_TARGET">
        <gen:ReferenceValue id="DIMENSION_DESCRIPTOR_VALUES_TARGET">
          <gen:DataKey>
            <com:KeyValue id="SERIES">
              <com:Value>_</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
            <com:KeyValue id="REPORTING_TYPE">
              <com:Value>N</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
            <com:KeyValue id="REF_AREA">
              <com:Value>704</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
          </gen:DataKey>
        </gen:ReferenceValue>
        <gen:ReferenceValue id="Dataflow">
          <gen:ObjectReference>
            <URN>urn:sdmx:org.sdmx.infomodel.datastructure.Dataflow=IAEG-SDGs:DF_SDG_GLC(1.4)</URN>
          </gen:ObjectReference>
        </gen:ReferenceValue>
      </gen:Target>
      <gen:AttributeSet>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="ORGANISATION_UNIT">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"/>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_INDICATOR_INFO">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"/>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"/>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="IND_DEF_CON_CLASS">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"/>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SRC_TYPE_COLL_METHOD">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"/>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="OTHER_METHOD">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"/>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_GOAL">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ <p> Goal 17: Strengthen implementation and promote global partnerships for sustainable development </p>]]></com:Text>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_TARGET">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ <p> Objective 17.2: Improve quality and added value in exports. Striving to achieve export growth rate of over 10%/year (global target 17.11)]]></com:Text>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_INDICATOR">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ <p> Indicator 17.2.1. Export value of goods </p>]]></com:Text>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="META_LAST_UPDATE">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ <p> June 2021 </p>]]></com:Text>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_ORGANISATION">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ <p> Chairperson: Ministry of Finance; </p>
 <p> - Coordination: General Statistics Office. </p>]]></com:Text>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_MAIL">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ <p> No. 28 Tran Hung Dao - Hoan Kiem District - Hanoi </p>]]></com:Text>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_EMAIL">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ <p> support@mof.gov.vn </p>]]></com:Text>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="STAT_CONC_DEF">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ <p> a) Concept </p>
 <p> Export goods include all domestically-originated goods and re-exported foreign goods, which are sent abroad, reducing the country&#39;s material and wealth sources. The export value of goods, calculated on FOB or equivalent terms, is the price of the goods up to the checkpoint of export (excluding international insurance and international freight), calculated for a period of time. specified and denominated in a unified currency, the US Dollar. In which: </p>
 <p> <strong> - </strong> Goods of domestic origin are goods that are exploited, produced or processed in the country according to Vietnam&#39;s regulations on origin; </p>
 <p> <strong> - </strong> Re-exported goods are goods of foreign origin that have been previously imported and counted as imported, then re-exported in their original state or simply processed, preserved, repacking, without changing the basic properties of the goods. </p>
 <p> b) Statistical Range </p>
 <p> Goods included in export statistics include: </p>
 <p> (1) Goods purchased/sold under ordinary commercial contracts signed with foreign <br>; </p>
 <p> (2) Goods in the form of barter with foreign countries, no payment methods are used; </p>
 <p> (3) Goods under processing and assembly contracts signed with foreign countries, with or without change of ownership, including: Finished products returned after processing or assembly; raw materials/supplies for export for processing and assembly; goods used as samples for processing and assembling; machinery and equipment directly serving processing and assembling, as agreed upon in the processing and assembly contract; </p>
 <p> (4) Goods in transactions between parent enterprises and subsidiaries, foreign direct investment branches, goods traded between buyers and sellers with a special relationship; </p>
 <p> (5) Re-exported goods: Foreign goods that have been imported and counted into imports before, and then exported in their original form or only preliminarily processed, preserved or repackaged without changing their properties. the basic nature of the goods, except for temporarily imported goods, which are subject to customs inspection and supervision and must be re-exported in accordance with law; </p>
 <p> (6) Exported goods in the form of loans, government and non-governmental aid, international organizations and other forms of humanitarian aid; </p>
 <p> (7) Goods under a financial leasing/leasing contract (machinery, equipment, means of transport), under which the lessee has the rights, responsibilities, risks, etc. related to the goods. If the above contents are not clearly defined in the contract, the lease term is 12 months or more; </p>
 <p> (8) Goods returned in export business (goods that were previously included in imports, then re-exported); </p>
 <p> (9) Goods temporarily exported for a period of time for temporary use for specific purposes but then converted to customs to not be re-imported. Such goods include: Goods for fairs, exhibitions, product introductions; documents for conferences, seminars, scientific research, education, sports competitions, cultural performances, art performances, medical examination and treatment, research and product development; means of transport, containers and transport-related equipment; other movable property; </p>
 <p> (10) Goods bought/sold or exchanged across borders, without commercial contracts; </p>
 <p> (11) Special goods: </p>
 <p> - Non-monetary gold: Is gold in the form of powder, bars, ingots, pieces, coins, gold jewelry, ... in the form of refined, raw or semi-processed by enterprises, commercial banks (except banks). goods, other organizations authorized to perform transactions by the State Bank of Vietnam) exported for the purpose of business, production, processing, processing, etc. in accordance with the law; </p>
 <p> - Banknotes, unissued securities, coins not or not yet put into circulation; coin or banknote collections; </p>
 <p> - Media for storing information and images: Magnetic tapes, magnetic discs, CD-ROMs, smart cards,... whether or not recorded audio, pictures, data, video games, software, etc. manufactured for the common use of all customers or for general purchase/sale without being specifically ordered (except for those manufactured to customer specific requirements or originals of movies, artwork, television programs, art performance programs, etc.); </p>
 <p> - Goods sent or received by post or courier service; </p>
 <p> - Exported electricity; </p>
 <p> - Exported goods using e-commerce methods: The exchange of information, ordering, signing of commercial contracts and payments with foreign countries is done via the Internet, but the goods are taken out of the territory of the country. territory of Vietnam, carrying out normal customs procedures, which are included in the statistics if the goods fall within the scope of the statistics; </p>
 <p> - Goods and fuel sold to foreign means of transport for use in international traffic; </p>
 <p> - Crude oil and minerals exploited in the continental shelf, Vietnam&#39;s exclusive economic zone, international waters, and overlapping areas are sold to foreign countries; </p>
 <p> - Drilling equipment sold offshore by enterprises without making customs declarations; </p>
 <p> - Airplanes, ships and other means of transport involved in transactions without making customs declarations; </p>
 <p> - Goods received and sent to international organizations (except goods sent between international organizations); </p>
 <p> - Goods being movable property, goods being luggage of people on exit must be declared according to regulations; </p>
 <p> - Waste and scrap of commercial value. </p>
 <p> - Satellite in case of change of ownership between domestic and foreign organizations and individuals; </p>
 <p> Goods not included in the statistics include: </p>
 <p> (1) Goods for export on the spot: Goods signed by Vietnamese traders to sell contracts with foreign traders but delivered in Vietnam as designated by foreign traders. </p>
 <p> (2) Goods purchased by Vietnamese traders from abroad and sold directly to third countries, goods that do not return to Vietnam or return to Vietnam but do not carry out normal export or import procedures at Vietnamese Customs Male. </p>
 <p> (3) Goods sold at duty free shops (Duty Free Shop). </p>
 <p> (4) Goods temporarily exported for a limited time and then re-imported such as: Goods for exhibitions, fairs, product introduction; documents for conferences, seminars, scientific research, education, sports competitions, cultural performances, art performances, medical examination and treatment, research and product development; means of transport, containers and transport-related equipment. </p>
 <p> (5) Goods are merely passing through the territory of Vietnam for the purpose of transshipment or transit. </p>
 <p> (6) Special goods include: </p>
 <p> - Goods under operating lease contracts (aircraft, ships, machinery and equipment): There is no transfer of ownership over the goods after the lease period; </p>
 <p> - Goods sent by the Vietnamese Government to diplomatic missions, consular missions, and representative offices at international organizations of Vietnam abroad; </p>
 <p> - Monetary gold: Gold in transactions of the State Bank of Vietnam or organizations authorized by the State Bank of Vietnam for export for the purpose of currency balance as prescribed by law; </p>
 <p> - Coins in circulation, banknotes, checks and issued securities in circulation; </p>
 <p> - Goods with the function of being an empty vehicle used to store goods: <br> Containers, boxes, bottles, jars and other types by revolving mode solely for the purpose of transporting goods; </p>
 <p> - Electronic products and contents (software, audio products, images, movies, e-books and others); </p>
 <p> - Intermediate media used to store information, images, contain software produced according to requests or private orders; </p>
 <p> - Goods brought to Vietnam&#39;s territory illegally; </p>
 <p> - Goods or take out of the customs territory of Vietnam for the purpose of repair or maintenance if such action does not change the origin of the goods; </p>
 <p> - Exported goods are weapons and equipment aimed at protecting national interests, sovereignty and security on the lists of state secrets; </p>
 <p> - Waste, scrap with no commercial value </p>]]></com:Text>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="UNIT_MEASURE">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ <p> million US dollars </p>]]></com:Text>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CLASS_SYSTEM">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ <p> The list of administrative units in Vietnam issued together with the Prime Minister&#39;s Decision No. 124/2004/QD-TTg dated July 8, 2004 and the changes updated by the General Statistics Office to date December 31, 2019) </p>
 <p> Vietnam&#39;s economic system in 2018 promulgated under Decision No. 27/2018/QD-TTg dated July 6, 2018 of the Prime Minister </p>
 <p> Standard classification of foreign trade </p>]]></com:Text>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SOURCE_TYPE">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ <p> - A customs dossier includes: The customs declaration or documents replacing the customs declaration; relevant documents such as: Goods sale and purchase contract, commercial invoice, transport document, certificate of origin and other relevant documents; </p>
 <p> - Information from the system of customs operations; </p>
 <p> - Reports of units under and under the General Department of Customs; </p>
 <p> - Information from state management agencies, carriers, associations, businesses and foreign agencies and organizations. </p>]]></com:Text>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="REL_CAL_POLICY">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ <p> Month, quarter, year. </p>]]></com:Text>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="DATA_SOURCE">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ <p> Ministry of Finance </p>]]></com:Text>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COMPILING_ORG">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ <p> Ministry of Finance </p>]]></com:Text>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="RATIONALE">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ <p> Is an indicator reflecting the amount of foreign currency that the country earns from export goods generated by the economy in a certain period. This indicator is used to assess the openness of the economy to the world market, the competitiveness of domestic production compared to other countries, the ability to access and penetrate the world commodity market. , at the same time creating favorable conditions for the import of machinery and equipment for technical and technological innovation and for the import of raw materials, materials and goods necessary for domestic production. </p>
 <p> In statistics, the export value of goods is an important indicator to calculate indicators in the national account system and the balance of international payments </p>]]></com:Text>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="DATA_COMP">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ <p> Calculation method </p>
 <p> Statistical time: Is the time when the customs office accepts the registration of the customs declaration. </p>
 <p> Changes in customs declarations during the implementation of customs procedures will be updated in the customs information system and adjusted in statistical reports. </p>
 <p> Statistical value of exported goods: The value developed by the customs authority for statistical purposes on the basis of the declared value and following the following principles: </p>
 <p> - Is the price of the goods up to the checkpoint of export, excluding international insurance and international freight charges (value calculated on FOB delivery terms or equivalent); </p>
 <p> - In case the statistical value of goods cannot be determined according to FOB or equivalent delivery conditions, the conversion shall be based on the customs dossier and other information sources. </p>
 <p> Determine statistical value in special cases </p>
 <p> - In case the customs declaration is registered once but exported many times, the statistical value is the actual value of the goods when exported; </p>
 <p> - Banknotes, coins and valuable papers not yet issued or put into circulation: Statistical value is the cost of producing banknotes, coins and valuable papers (not is the face value of these banknotes, coins or valuable papers); </p>
 <p> - Media for information storage includes: Magnetic tapes, magnetic discs, CD-ROMs, smart cards and other media whether or not containing information, other than those manufactured to order or separate orders: Statistics on the full customs value of these goods (not just the value of the uninformed intermediary); </p>
 <p> - For goods that are allowed to record a provisional price when registering the customs declaration, the statistical value must be adjusted when there is an official price on the amended and supplemented declaration; </p>
 <p> - Processed, processed and assembled goods: Calculate the value of all raw goods before processing, processing and assembling and the entire value of finished products returned after processing, processing and assembly; </p>
 <p> - Transactions that do not declare value (for example, barter goods, humanitarian aid goods, etc.), the value of goods in statistics is calculated according to the principles of customs valuation; </p>
 <p> - Exported electricity: The statistical value is the value declared on the customs declaration; </p>
 <p> - Goods under a finance lease: Calculate the value of the goods on the basis of the selling price of similar goods (excluding services provided under the lease such as training, maintenance, financial fees); </p>
 <p> - Goods and services: Statistical value determined at the FOB or equivalent price (for exports) of the goods and excluding service charges; </p>
 <p> Currency and exchange rate: Statistical value of exported goods in US Dollars (USD). The customs authority shall base itself on the current regulations on taxable exchange rates for exported goods to convert foreign currencies used in statistics. </p>
 <p> Quantitative unit: Use units specified in the List of exported and imported goods of Vietnam. </p>
 <p> For the converted quantity unit used in statistical forms: Different units of quantity are converted to the uniform unit in the form based on the data from the customs dossier. </p>]]></com:Text>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COVERAGE">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ <p> - Annual figures from 2014-2019 </p>
 <p> - Data available for subcategories: economic sector; standard classification table of foreign trade; economic sector; group of goods; body of water/territory </p>
 <p> (Published source: Statistical Yearbook of the General Statistics Office) </p>]]></com:Text>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COMPARABILITY">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ <p> This indicator reflects Vietnam&#39;s sustainable development goals (target 17.2). The set of global sustainable development indicators does not have this indicator. </p>]]></com:Text>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="OTHER_DOC">
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ <p> - Circular No. 03/2019/TT-BKHDT dated January 22, 2019 stipulating the set of statistical indicators for sustainable development of Vietnam; </p>
 <p> - <a href="https://unstats.un.org/sdgs/metadata/"> https://unstats.un.org/sdgs/metadata/ </a> </p>]]></com:Text>
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
      </gen:AttributeSet>
    </gen:Report>
  </mes:MetadataSet>
</mes:GenericMetadata>