<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>All metadata fields for indicator 1-2-3, translated into all languages</message>
	<data>
		<languages>
			<language lang="en"> &lt;p&gt; Common Goal 1: End all forms of poverty everywhere &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Target 1.2: Nationally implement appropriate social security systems and measures for all, including social security policies, and achieve substantial coverage by 2030 poor and vulnerable (Global 1.3 target) &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Indicator 1.2.3. Number of people receiving monthly social support in the community &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; June 2021. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Ministry of Labour, Invalids and Social Affairs. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; 12 Ngo Quyen, Hoan Kiem, Hanoi &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; banbientap@molisa.gov.vn &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Monthly social allowance beneficiaries include: &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; (1) Children under 16 years of age without a source of nourishment in one of the following cases: &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; a) Abandoned without adoption; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; b) Orphaned both father and mother; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; c) Orphaned father or mother and the other missing as prescribed by law; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; d) Orphaned father or mother and the other who is enjoying the care and nurturing regime at social protection establishments or social houses; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; dd) Orphaned father or mother and the other person is serving a prison sentence in prison or is serving a decision on handling of administrative violations at reformatory, compulsory education institution, establishment compulsory detoxification; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; e) Both parents are missing as prescribed by law; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; f) Both parents are receiving care and nurturing regime at social protection establishments or social houses; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; g) Both parents are serving prison sentences in prisons or are serving decisions on handling of administrative violations at reformatories, compulsory education establishments, compulsory detoxification establishments; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; h) The parent is missing as prescribed by law and the other person is enjoying the care and nurturing regime at a social protection establishment or social house; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; i) One parent is missing as prescribed by law and the other is serving a prison sentence at a prison or is serving a decision on handling of administrative violations at a reformatory or educational institution. compulsory education, compulsory detoxification establishments; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; k) One parent is enjoying the care and nurturing regime at a social protection establishment or social house and the other is serving a prison sentence at a prison or is serving a handling decision administrative violations at reformatory schools, compulsory educational institutions, compulsory detoxification establishments. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; (2) Persons aged between 16 and 22 years old who fall into one of the cases specified in item (1) and are studying in high school, vocational training, professional secondary school, college or university with a first degree. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; (3) Children living with HIV from poor households; HIV-infected people from poor households who are no longer able to work without pension, monthly social insurance allowance, monthly preferential allowance for meritorious people, or other monthly allowance. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; (4) People from poor households with no husband or wife; have a dead husband or wife; whose husband or wife is missing as prescribed by law and is raising a child under 16 years old or is raising a child aged between 16 and 22 years old but that child is in high school, vocational training, professional secondary school, college, university study first degree. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; (5) Elderly person in one of the following cases: &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; a) An elderly person in a poor household has no person with the obligation and right to serve or has a person with the obligation and the right to serve but this person is enjoying a monthly social allowance; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; b) Persons who are full 80 years old or older not specified in item a but do not have a monthly pension, social insurance allowance or monthly social allowance; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; c) Elderly people from poor households have no person to take care of, have no conditions to live in the community, are eligible for admission to social protection establishments or social houses but have caregivers. care in the community. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; (6) Disabled children and disabled people are entitled to social allowances in accordance with the law on disabled people. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Person &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; The list of administrative units of Vietnam 2010 issued together with the Prime Minister&apos;s Decision No. 124/2004/QD-TTg dated July 8, 2004 and the changes updated by the General Statistics Office to date. point of December 31, 2019. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Statistical reporting regime issued by the Ministry of Labor, Invalids and Social Affairs. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; The Ministry of Labour, Invalids and Social Affairs shall issue a report form and send it to the Departments of Labor, Invalids and Social Affairs of the provinces/cities directly under the Central Government for implementation on an annual basis. A unit under the Ministry of Labour, Invalids and Social Affairs was assigned the task of synthesizing data sent back from the Departments to calculate the target. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Year &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; The indicator reflects the number of people receiving monthly social support nationwide in a year, on that basis, providing information for better management and policy making of social support, contributing part to improve the lives of the supported subjects. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Only data for 2019 for certain target groups are Elderly; people with disabilities and children. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; There are no complete data for each subgroup. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; (Published source: SDG 2020 Country Report, Data from the Ministry of Labour, Invalids and Social Affairs). &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Similar to VSDGI 1.2.1, this indicator reflects part of the global SDG target “1.3.1. Proportion of population covered by social protection floors/systems, by sex, distinguishing children, unemployed persons, older persons, persons with disabilities, pregnant women, newborns, work-injury victims and the poor and the vulnerable”. &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; Due to the specificity of Vietnam, there is no clear concept of the term &quot;social protection&quot;. Social protection is close to the concept of social assistance, which is one of the three basic pillars of the welfare system. With the purpose of overcoming risks, social assistance together with social insurance have the function of reducing risks, and proactive labor market policies to prevent risks for people. Therefore, to replace the global indicator 1.3.1, Vietnam uses this indicator along with some related indicators of Vietnam such as: &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; 1.2.1. Number of people paying social insurance, health insurance and unemployment insurance &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; 1.2.2. Number of people entitled to social insurance, health insurance and unemployment insurance &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; 1.2.4. Number of people receiving unexpected social support &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; 1.2.5. Number of people being concentratedly raised in social protection establishments and social houses &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; - Circular No. 03/2019/TT-BKHĐT dated January 22, 2019 stipulating the set of statistical indicators for sustainable development of Vietnam; &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; - https://unstats.un.org/sdgs/metadata/ &lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
			<language lang="vi">&lt;p&gt;Mục tiêu chung 1: Chấm dứt mọi hình thức nghèo ở mọi nơi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mục tiêu 1.2: Triển khai trên toàn quốc các hệ thống và các biện pháp an sinh xã hội thích hợp cho mọi người, bao gồm cả các chính sách an sinh xã hội và đến năm 2030 đạt được diện bao phủ đáng kể cho người nghèo và những người dễ bị tổn thương (Mục tiêu 1.3 toàn cầu)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chỉ tiêu 1.2.3. Số người được hỗ trợ xã hội hàng tháng tại cộng đồng&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tháng 6/2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bộ Lao động, Thương binh và Xã hội.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;12 Ngô Quyền, Hoàn Kiếm, Hà Nội&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;banbientap@molisa.gov.vn&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Đối tượng hưởng trợ cấp xã hội hàng tháng gồm:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1) Trẻ em dưới 16 tuổi không có nguồn nuôi dưỡng thuộc một trong các trường hợp quy định sau đây:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a) Bị bỏ rơi chưa có người nhận làm con nuôi;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b) Mồ côi cả cha và mẹ;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;c) Mồ côi cha hoặc mẹ và người còn lại mất tích theo quy định của pháp luật;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;d) Mồ côi cha hoặc mẹ và người còn lại đang hưởng chế độ chăm sóc, nuôi dưỡng tại cơ sở bảo trợ xã hội, nhà xã hội;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;đ) Mồ côi cha hoặc mẹ và người còn lại đang trong thời gian chấp hành án phạt tù tại trại giam hoặc đang chấp hành quyết định xử lý vi phạm hành chính tại trường giáo dưỡng, cơ sở giáo dục bắt buộc, cơ sở cai nghiện bắt buộc;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;e) Cả cha và mẹ mất tích theo quy định của pháp luật;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;f) Cả cha và mẹ đang hưởng chế độ chăm sóc, nuôi dưỡng tại cơ sở bảo trợ xã hội, nhà xã hội;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;g) Cả cha và mẹ đang trong thời gian chấp hành án phạt tù tại trại giam hoặc đang chấp hành quyết định xử lý vi phạm hành chính tại trường giáo dưỡng, cơ sở giáo dục bắt buộc, cơ sở cai nghiện bắt buộc;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;h) Cha hoặc mẹ mất tích theo quy định của pháp luật và người còn lại đang hưởng chế độ chăm sóc, nuôi dưỡng tại cơ sở bảo trợ xã hội, nhà xã hội;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;i) Cha hoặc mẹ mất tích theo quy định của pháp luật và người còn lại đang trong thời gian chấp hành án phạt tù tại trại giam hoặc đang chấp hành quyết định xử lý vi phạm hành chính tại trường giáo dưỡng, cơ sở giáo dục bắt buộc, cơ sở cai nghiện bắt buộc;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;k) Cha hoặc mẹ đang hưởng chế độ chăm sóc, nuôi dưỡng tại cơ sở bảo trợ xã hội, nhà xã hội và người còn lại đang trong thời gian chấp hành án phạt tù tại trại giam hoặc đang chấp hành quyết định xử lý vi phạm hành chính tại trường giáo dưỡng, cơ sở giáo dục bắt buộc, cơ sở cai nghiện bắt buộc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(2) Người từ 16 tuổi đến 22 tuổi thuộc một trong các trường hợp quy định tại mục (1) mà đang học phổ thông, học nghề, trung học chuyên nghiệp, cao đẳng, đại học văn bằng thứ nhất.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(3) Trẻ em bị nhiễm HIV thuộc hộ nghèo; người bị nhiễm HIV thuộc hộ nghèo không còn khả năng lao động mà không có lương hưu, trợ cấp bảo hiểm xã hội hàng tháng, trợ cấp ưu đãi người có công hàng tháng, trợ cấp hàng tháng khác.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(4) Người thuộc hộ nghèo không có chồng hoặc không có vợ; có chồng hoặc vợ đã chết; có chồng hoặc vợ mất tích theo quy định của pháp luật và đang nuôi con dưới 16 tuổi hoặc đang nuôi con từ 16 tuổi đến 22 tuổi nhưng người con đó đang học phổ thông, học nghề, trung học chuyên nghiệp, cao đẳng, đại học văn bằng thứ nhất.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(5) Người cao tuổi thuộc một trong các trường hợp sau đây:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a) Người cao tuổi thuộc hộ nghèo không có người có nghĩa vụ và quyền phụng dưỡng hoặc có người có nghĩa vụ và quyền phụng dưỡng nhưng người nàyđang hưởng chế độ trợ cấp xã hội hàng tháng;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b) Người từ đủ 80 tuổi trở lên không thuộc diện quy định tại mục a mà không có lương hưu, trợ cấp bảo hiểm xã hội hàng tháng, trợ cấp xã hội hàng tháng;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;c) Người cao tuổi thuộc hộ nghèo không có người có nghĩa vụ và quyền phụng dưỡng, không có điều kiện sống ở cộng đồng, đủ điều kiện tiếp nhận vào cơ sở bảo trợ xã hội, nhà xã hội nhưng có người nhận chăm sóc tại cộng đồng.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(6) Trẻ em khuyết tật, người khuyết tật thuộc diện hưởng trợ cấp xã hội theo quy định của pháp luật về người khuyết tật.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Người&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bảng danh mục các đơn vị hành chính Việt Nam 2010 ban hành kèm theo Quyết định số 124/2004/QĐ-TTg ngày 08/7/2004 của Thủ tướng Chính phủ và những thay đổi được Tổng cục Thống kê cập nhật đến thời điểm 31/12/2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chế độ báo cáo thống kê do Bộ Lao động, Thương binh và Xã hội ban hành.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bộ Lao động Thương binh và Xã hội ban hành biểu mẫu báo cáo gửi Sở Lao động, Thương binh và Xã hội các tỉnh/thành phố trực thuộc Trung ương thực hiện theo định kỳ hàng năm. Một đơn vị thuộc Bộ Lao động Thương binh và Xã hội được giao nhiệm vụ tổng hợp số liệu từ các Sở gửi về để tính chỉ tiêu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Năm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chỉ tiêu phản ánh số người được hỗ trợ xã hội hàng tháng trong phạm vi cả nước trong năm, trên cơ sở đó cung cấp thông tin phục vụ cho công tác quản lý và hoạch định chính sách hỗ trợ xã hội tốt hơn, góp phần cải thiện đời sống cho các đối tượng được hỗ trợ.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chỉ có số liệu của năm 2019 cho một số nhóm đối tượng là Người cao tuổi; người khuyết tật và trẻ em.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chưa có số liệu đầy đủ cho từng phân tổ.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Nguồn công bố: Báo cáo quốc gia SDG 2020. Số liệu từ Bộ Lao động, Thương binh và Xã hội).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tương tự chỉ tiêu VSDGI 1.2.1, chỉ tiêu này phản ánh 1 phần của chỉ tiêu SDG toàn cầu “1.3.1. Proportion of population covered by social protection floors/systems, by sex, distinguishing children, unemployed persons, older persons, persons with disabilities, pregnant women, newborns, work-injury victims and the poor and the vulnerable” của quốc tế. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do đặc thù Việt Nam không có khái niệm rõ ràng về thuật ngữ “bảo trợ xã hội”. Bảo trợ xã hội gần với khái niệm trợ giúp xã hội, là một trong ba trụ cột cơ bản của hệ thống an sinh. Với mục đích khắc phục rủi ro, trợ giúp xã hội cùng với bảo hiểm xã hội có chức năng giảm thiểu rủi ro, và chính sách thị trường lao động chủ động nhằm phòng ngừa rủi ro cho người dân. Vì vậy, để thay thế cho chỉ tiêu 1.3.1 toàn cầu, Việt Nam sử dụng chỉ tiêu này cùng một số chỉ tiêu liên quan của Việt Nam như:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.2.1. Số người đóng bảo hiểm xã hội, bảo hiểm y tế, bảo hiểm thất nghiệp&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.2.2. Số người được hưởng bảo hiểm xã hội, bảo hiểm y tế, bảo hiểm thất nghiệp&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.2.4. Số người được hỗ trợ xã hội đột xuất&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.2.5. Số người được nuôi dưỡng tập trung trong cơ sở bảo trợ xã hội, nhà xã hội&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Thông tư số 03/2019/TT-BKHĐT ngày 22/01/2019 quy định Bộ chỉ tiêu thống kê phát triển bền vững của Việt Nam;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- https://unstats.un.org/sdgs/metadata/&lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
</languages>
</data>
</root>
